// Questions for Geography
const QBANK_GEOGRAPHY = [
  {
    prompt: "Who was Justinian?",
    options: ["Jesus's father", "a Jewish rabbi", "a Christian missionary", "a Roman emperor"],
    answer: 3,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Early Christian communities were led by",
    options: ["bishops", "saints", "rabbis", "pharaohs"],
    answer: 0,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Conflicts between kings forced Israel to break into two kingdomsâ€”Israel and",
    options: ["Jerusalem", "Canaan", "Judah", "Byzantium"],
    answer: 2,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Whom do the Hebrews claim as their ancestor?",
    options: ["Paul", "Theodora", "Abraham", "Moses"],
    answer: 2,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "The Torah is the first part of",
    options: ["the Hebrew Bible", "the Gospels", "Justinian's Code", "the New Testament"],
    answer: 0,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "The Resurrection is the Christian belief that Jesus",
    options: ["was crucified", "performed miracles", "taught about salvation", "rose from the dead"],
    answer: 3,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Christianity spread throughout the Roman Empire after",
    options: ["riots against Justinian", "invasion of Ottoman Turks", "the conversion of Constantine", "different denominations were formed"],
    answer: 2,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "During which Jewish holiday do Jews celebrate the Exodus?",
    options: ["Hanukkah", "Passover", "Rosh Hashanah", "Yom Kippur"],
    answer: 1,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "According to the Bible, Jesus was born in",
    options: ["Constantinople", "Bethlehem", "Damascus", "Rome"],
    answer: 1,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "According to the Bible, God promised Abraham that",
    options: ["he would build a great temple", "he would lead Hebrews out of Egypt", "he would be victorious", "his descendants would be a mighty nation"],
    answer: 3,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "The Hebrews viewed their release from slavery as",
    options: ["fulfillment of prophesy", "God's justice", "sign that God was protecting them", "sign of Moses's great leadership"],
    answer: 2,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "When he was about 30, Jesus",
    options: ["began to travel and teach", "was arrested", "was crucified", "studied carpentry with Joseph"],
    answer: 0,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Why was Jesus arrested?",
    options: ["He supported Roman Empire", "He challenged authority of political/religious leaders", "He challenged Mosaic law", "Roman Empire discriminated against Jews"],
    answer: 1,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "Jesus feeding a huge crowd with small amount of food is an example of",
    options: ["a Passover meal", "a mosaic", "a miracle", "a parable"],
    answer: 2,
    points: 1
  },
  {
    prompt: "There are many Christian denominations because",
    options: ["people interpreted Jesus's teachings differently", "Jesus divided his followers into groups", "Paul encouraged Churches to find own truths", "Roman empire was divided into states"],
    answer: 0,
    points: 1
  },
];
